Friends, in today's video we will
discuss the technical aspects of ICICI Lombard Insurance. If you
want to buy this stock for the long term, it will give you very good returns.
It is a very good leader in the insurance sector
and its market capitalization is quite good.
If you want to buy it for the short term, then
in this video we will provide the level,
stoploss, and target.
With a stoploss target of 19, you
can consider buying it. Before buying,
please do your own research and
consult your financial advisor.
This video is for educational purposes only. Let me
tell you here that
today, on the day of fast trading,
I am going to
add a good quantity of this stock to my portfolio. So,
you can also
invest in it after consulting your financial advisor. So
let's start today's
video. Let's
grow some support and resistance levels here.
Here we have plotted its Delhi chart.
First of all, we
plot it in the Delhi chart.
Look at the Delhi chart here, this train line.  It has
currently taken support here three times, you
can see that the
stock is moving upwards with 123.30 and the
most important thing is that here we connect their registers,
so here you can see
that it took support here twice and
also took resistance here, it fell
but now you can see that due to the beach scandal,
this stock has united here, so
now it can go upwards and here
we draw more support in it, by
drawing a train line from below, let us
take this site smaller i.e. weekly chart,
here we will
see it more clearly, so from here we have it, which
started taking support from 2018, from here we grow the train line,
so see here how many
times it has taken support, 1234, that is, for the time
you took support, the fall of which we can
see in it, has the support come here,
on an according basis, this
stock went upwards from around this support,
after this you can see
12345  Time to do this, here this stock has
taken support and the most important
thing here can be seen in the weekly chart, it is a
price reduction candle, that is, its
body is company and Shahdol has formed higher from below
and in this you can see that its high has also been
broken,
1525 was the high of Scandal and here we
can see its high 1534, that is, we have got complete
confirmation, to buy in this topic,
now we start in its Delhi chart that is
here and let's see the support in it, is
some support coming out, so here
this stock has reversed from a major support, the
train line that we had
drawn here, it had acted as resistance here earlier also, so this
area is its
major support, so number 1, it is not confirmed
that it has reversed from its support,
number 2, here in the Delhi chart there is an
Amar candle and that too has
formed with confirmation, number 3, here you can see
that it has backed out of the assistant line from above
and here it has
another resistance.  The
price at which this stock is trading is giving it
a resistance here also, we draw a line here,
see here it has
taken a resistance, this entire area was a
resistance, here also this resistance on the assistant
is a failure and then the stock
comes downwards again, it
breaks out, for that the stop keeps
moving above it, from here we
can see this stock many times, support level, then
in the last it was seen looking downwards, there is a
resistance for it, but this
candle faced the assistant, now
here these three drops Ishq channel are formed, so from
here it seems to go upwards,
but we can set it with stop loss,
so I will show you one more
thing here, in the weekly chart
here you can see, in the weekly chart, free
period moving average, here a very good
support is coming out, then see at 12345
water, taking this support of this moving average 15 times, the
stock went upwards, it went up by forming 12 June
pattern, here also it went
up by forming Doji pattern  Here also it went
up by forming a Doji pattern and here also you
can see that by forming this pattern the stock
is moving upwards and we
can think of buying in this. Now let us talk about stop loss
and target in this, so our
stop loss will be around 100 points, that is,
its support, this is a major support here, so we will
keep the stop loss near this and our first
target will be around 1600 rupees, so
with that target you can buy for the short term,
if you want to buy for the long term then
this is a very good opportunity to
buy in this stock, so let
us see our stop loss here, how much does it come,
our stop loss is coming out to be ₹90,
so how will you calculate here that
in what quantity we have to work, so
suppose I can take a risk of 2,000 here,
but for the trend, here 2000
divided by here, whatever will be your stop loss here,
whatever will be your stop loss here  The stoploss was 90, so
here you will work only in 22 quantity,
so you will not work more than this
because you want to take maximum loss of 2000 here,
so here we can see that if we
work in 22 quantity, then
whatever our current price is here, we will
multiply it with it, our total
investment will come, so our
current price here is around Rs 1530, so
here multiply
1530 by two, then our total investment here will be
3000, so in this way you should
calculate your stoploss target in advance
and how much risk you want to take, only after
calculating this you should invest in any stock, be it
for short term or for
intraday, whatever I give, it can be from
one to 2 to 3 minutes
and if you buy in it, then
definitely do your own English typing, if you
liked the video then like the video
and subscribe to the channel.